Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
- Box: 43, Folder: 59, Publication (Box 43, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: Supervisor's Conference, 1965; Publication (Box 43, Folder 59)
- Box: 43, Folder: 60, Publication (Box 43, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: Handbook, Publication (Box 43, Folder 60)
- Box: 43, Folder: 61, Publication (Box 43, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: School of Engineering, 1960; Publication (Box 43, Folder 61)
- Box: 43, Folder: 62, Publication (Box 43, Folder 62)
  - Item 1: Driver's Manual, 1954; Publication (Box 43, Folder 62)
- Box: 43, Folder: 63, Publication (Box 43, Folder 63)
  - Item 1: Handbook, 1960; Publication (Box 43, Folder 63)
- Box: 43, Folder: 64, Publication (Box 43, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: Profit and Our Business, 1956; Publication (Box 43, Folder 64)
- Box: 43, Folder: 65, Publication (Box 43, Folder 65)
  - Item 1: How To Show Films, 1956; Publication (Box 43, Folder 65)
- Box: 43, Folder: 66, Publication (Box 43, Folder 66)
  - Item 1: Medical Department, 1968; Publication (Box 43, Folder 66)
- Box: 43, Folder: 67, Publication (Box 43, Folder 67)
  - Item 1: Employees' Pensions, Disability Benefits and Death Benefits, 1969; Publication (Box 43, Folder 67)
- Box: 43, Folder: 68, Publication (Box 43, Folder 68)
  - Item 1: Cue on Colds, Publication (Box 43, Folder 68)
- Box: 43, Folder: 69, Publication (Box 43, Folder 69)
  - Item 1: Eyes Right, Publication (Box 43, Folder 69)
- Box: 43, Folder: 70, Publication (Box 43, Folder 70)
  - Item 1: Fresh Air Vs. Illness, Publication (Box 43, Folder 70)
- Box: 43, Folder: 71, Publication (Box 43, Folder 71)
  - Item 1: 6 Steps To Proper Weight, 1956; Publication (Box 43, Folder 71)
- Box: 43, Folder: 72, Publication (Box 43, Folder 72)
  - Item 1: Group Life Insurance, 1960; Publication (Box 43, Folder 72)
- Box: 43, Folder: 73, Publication (Box 43, Folder 73)
  - Item 1: Take Care Of Your Hearing, 1956; Publication (Box 43, Folder 73)
- Box: 43, Folder: 74, Publication (Box 43, Folder 74)
  - Item 1: Savings Bonds, 1956; Publication (Box 43, Folder 74)
- Box: 43, Folder: 75, Publication (Box 43, Folder 75)
  - Item 1: The Toughest Muscle In The Body, 1956; Publication (Box 43, Folder 75)
- Box: 43, Folder: 76, Publication (Box 43, Folder 76)
  - Item 1: Hospital Benefits, 1960; Publication (Box 43, Folder 76)
- Box: 43, Folder: 77, Publication (Box 43, Folder 77)
  - Item 1: The Ounce of Prevention, Publication (Box 43, Folder 77)
- Box: 43, Folder: 78, Publication (Box 43, Folder 78)
  - Item 1: Cuts and Bruises, Publication (Box 43, Folder 78)
- Box: 43, Folder: 79, Publication (Box 43, Folder 79)
  - Item 1: United Medical Service Benefits, 1960; Publication (Box 43, Folder 79)
- Box: 43, Folder: 80, Publication (Box 43, Folder 80)
  - Item 1: Veterans Insurance, 1956; Publication (Box 43, Folder 80)
- Box: 43, Folder: 81, Publication (Box 43, Folder 81)
  - Item 1: Benefits, Publication (Box 43, Folder 81)
- Box: 43, Folder: 82, Publication (Box 43, Folder 82)
  - Item 1: Diabetes Can Happen To You, 1955; Publication (Box 43, Folder 82)
- Box: 43, Folder: 83, Publication (Box 43, Folder 83)
  - Item 1: Two-Day Conference Leadership Training, 1952; Publication (Box 43, Folder 83)
- Box: 43, Folder: 84, Publication (Box 43, Folder 84)
  - Item 1: How To Cure Constipation, Publication (Box 43, Folder 84)
- Box: 43, Folder: 85, Publication (Box 43, Folder 85)
  - Item 1: Employee Induction, 1954; Publication (Box 43, Folder 85)
- Box: 44, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Class Title and Ranges, 1965; Publication (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Box: 44, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Summary of Activities, 1964; Publication (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Box: 44, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Scholarship Program For Sons and Daughters of Company Members, Publication (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Box: 44, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Employees' Retirement Plan, 1966; Publication (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Box: 44, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance Plan, 1961; Publication (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Box: 44, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Group Hospitalization and Surgical Benefits, 1961; Publication (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Box: 44, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Circle of Safety Pays Of For El Reno, 1963; Publication (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Box: 44, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Circle of Safety Bulletin, Publication (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Box: 44, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Flash Bulletin, 1965; Publication (Box 44, Folder 9)
- Box: 44, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Final Report, 1965; Publication (Box 44, Folder 10)
- Box: 44, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Circle of Safety Bulletin, 1965; Publication (Box 44, Folder 11)
- Box: 44, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Evening Study Courses, 1967; Publication (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Box: 44, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Manual For Job Evaluation, 1967; Publication (Box 44, Folder 13)
- Box: 44, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Pay Plan, 1966; Publication (Box 44, Folder 14)
- Box: 44, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The O.L. Retirement Club, 1957; Publication (Box 44, Folder 15)
- Box: 44, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Pension Plan, 1969; Publication (Box 44, Folder 16)
- Box: 44, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance Plan, 1968; Publication (Box 44, Folder 17)
- Box: 44, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Your Leisure Time Handbook, 1969; Publication (Box 44, Folder 18)
- Box: 44, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Pension Plan, 1963; Publication (Box 44, Folder 19)
- Box: 44, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: New Democratic Party Constitution, 1975; Publication (Box 44, Folder 20)
- Box: 44, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: New Hospital and Surgical Benefits, 1955; Publication (Box 44, Folder 21)
- Box: 44, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: British Columbia Gov't Employees Union Constitution, 1975; Publication (Box 44, Folder 22)
- Box: 44, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance Plan, 1970; Publication (Box 44, Folder 23)
- Box: 44, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance Plan, 1962; Publication (Box 44, Folder 24)
- Box: 44, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Pension Plan, 1960; Publication (Box 44, Folder 25)
- Box: 44, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Ontario Federation of Labor, 1978; Publication (Box 44, Folder 26)
- Box: 44, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Your Group Life Insurance, 1969; Publication (Box 44, Folder 27)
- Box: 44, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Your Pension Plan, 1969; Publication (Box 44, Folder 28)
- Box: 44, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Instructions For Excavating, 1956; Publication (Box 44, Folder 29)
- Box: 44, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Accounting Principles, 1959; Publication (Box 44, Folder 30)
- Box: 44, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Men and Administration, 1959; Publication (Box 44, Folder 31)
- Box: 44, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Transformer Bank Connections, 1957; Publication (Box 44, Folder 32)
- Box: 44, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Report of Salary and Wage Survey, 1964; Publication (Box 44, Folder 33)
- Box: 44, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Positions In Oregon State Government, 1959; Publication (Box 44, Folder 34)
- Box: 44, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 44, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Organization For Rehabilitation Through Training, 1962; Publication (Box 44, Folder 35)
- Box: 44, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 44, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Medical Expense Insurance Plan, 1952; Publication (Box 44, Folder 36)
- Box: 44, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 44, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Tuition Refund Program, 1966; Publication (Box 44, Folder 37)
- Box: 44, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 44, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Medicare Benefits, 1971; Publication (Box 44, Folder 38)
- Box: 44, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 44, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance Plan, 1968; Publication (Box 44, Folder 39)
- Box: 44, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 44, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Comprehensive Medical Expense Benefit Plan For Persons Under 65, 1970; Publication (Box 44, Folder 40)
- Box: 44, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 44, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Bulletin, 1965; Publication (Box 44, Folder 41)
- Box: 44, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 44, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Long Term Disability Income Insurance For Salaried Employees, 1971; Publication (Box 44, Folder 42)
- Box: 44, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 44, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Your Basic Retirement Plan, 1970; Publication (Box 44, Folder 43)
- Box: 44, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 44, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Student Training, 1967; Publication (Box 44, Folder 44)
- Box: 44, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 44, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Day By Day Schedule, Publication (Box 44, Folder 45)
- Box: 44, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 44, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Production Division Student Program, 1958; Publication (Box 44, Folder 46)
- Box: 44, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 44, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Student Training, 1958; Publication (Box 44, Folder 47)
- Box: 44, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 44, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Student Training, 1963; Publication (Box 44, Folder 48)
- Box: 44, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 44, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Engineering Training Program, 1958; Publication (Box 44, Folder 49)
- Box: 44, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 44, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Protection and Security, 1967; Publication (Box 44, Folder 50)
- Box: 44, Folder: 51, Publication (Box 44, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: Protection and Security, 1966; Publication (Box 44, Folder 51)
- Box: 44, Folder: 52, Publication (Box 44, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: The Progress Interview, 1960; Publication (Box 44, Folder 52)
- Box: 44, Folder: 53, Publication (Box 44, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: Salary Administration Program, 1962; Publication (Box 44, Folder 53)
- Box: 44, Folder: 54, Publication (Box 44, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: Pension Plan A+B, Publication (Box 44, Folder 54)
- Box: 44, Folder: 55, Publication (Box 44, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: Important Improvements in Your Retirement Plan and Group Insurance Plan, 1959; Publication (Box 44, Folder 55)
- Box: 44, Folder: 56, Publication (Box 44, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: Savings and Stock Investment Plan, 1960; Publication (Box 44, Folder 56)
- Box: 44, Folder: 57, Publication (Box 44, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: Retirement Plan, 1959; Publication (Box 44, Folder 57)
- Box: 44, Folder: 58, Publication (Box 44, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: New MajorMedical Expense Benefits, 1956; Publication (Box 44, Folder 58)
- Box: 44, Folder: 59, Publication (Box 44, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: Insurance Program, 1960; Publication (Box 44, Folder 59)
- Box: 44, Folder: 60, Publication (Box 44, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: Savings and Stock Investment Plan, 1966; Publication (Box 44, Folder 60)
- Box: 44, Folder: 61, Publication (Box 44, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: Retirement Plan for hourly Employees, 1970; Publication (Box 44, Folder 61)
- Box: 44, Folder: 62, Publication (Box 44, Folder 62)
  - Item 1: Retirement Plan for salaried Employees, 1970; Publication (Box 44, Folder 62)
- Box: 44, Folder: 63, Publication (Box 44, Folder 63)
  - Item 1: Hourly Employees' Retirement Plan, 1969; Publication (Box 44, Folder 63)
- Box: 44, Folder: 64, Publication (Box 44, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: Owens-Corning Group Insurance Plan, 1972; Publication (Box 44, Folder 64)
- Box: 44, Folder: 65, Publication (Box 44, Folder 65)
  - Item 1: Owens-Corning Group insurance Plan, 1972; Publication (Box 44, Folder 65)
- Box: 44, Folder: 66, Publication (Box 44, Folder 66)
  - Item 1: Owens-Corning Fiberglass Corporation Salaried Employees' Retirement Plan, 1969; Publication (Box 44, Folder 66)
- Box: 44, Folder: 67, Publication (Box 44, Folder 67)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance, 1954; Publication (Box 44, Folder 67)
  - Item 2: Group Insurance, 1956; Publication (Box 44, Folder 67)
  - Item 3: Owens-Illinois Contributory Retirement Plan, 1963; Publication (Box 44, Folder 67)
  - Item 4: A Savings and Loan Plan, Publication (Box 44, Folder 67)
  - Item 5: Money Plus Your Salary Benefits, Publication (Box 44, Folder 67)
  - Item 6: Monthly Checks for Life, Publication (Box 44, Folder 67)
  - Item 7: Contributory Retirement Plan, 1955; Publication (Box 44, Folder 67)
  - Item 8: Major Medical Expense Benefits, 1956; Publication (Box 44, Folder 67)
  - Item 9: Owens-Illinois Service Retirement Plan for Salaried Employees, 1962; Publication (Box 44, Folder 67)
  - Item 10: Key to Your Leisure Time, Publication (Box 44, Folder 67)
  - Item 11: Owens-Illinois Scholarships, Publication (Box 44, Folder 67)
- Box: 44, Folder: 68, Publication (Box 44, Folder 68)
  - Item 1: Hourly Job Evaluation Program, Publication (Box 44, Folder 68)
  - Item 2: To Holders of Owens-Illinois Salary Administration Program Brochure, 1964; Publication (Box 44, Folder 68)
  - Item 3: The Salary Benefits of, Publication (Box 44, Folder 68)
  - Item 4: Money Plus Your Salary Benefits, 1958; Publication (Box 44, Folder 68)
  - Item 5: Wage and Salary Administration, 1963; Publication (Box 44, Folder 68)
  - Item 6: To Holders of Owens-Illinois Salary Administration Program Brochure, 1965; Publication (Box 44, Folder 68)
  - Item 7: To Holders of Owens-Illinois Salary Administration Program Brochure, 1966; Publication (Box 44, Folder 68)
  - Item 8: To Holders of Owens-Illinois Salary Administration Program Brochure, 1964; Publication (Box 44, Folder 68)
- Box: 44, Folder: 69, Publication (Box 44, Folder 69)
  - Item 1: Staff Handbook for Service Employees, 1966; Publication (Box 44, Folder 69)
  - Item 2: Reading Improvement for Elementary, Secondary, and College Levels, Publication (Box 44, Folder 69)
  - Item 3: The Executive Program for the City of New York and the Metropolitan Area, 1964; Publication (Box 44, Folder 69)
- Box: 44, Folder: 70, Publication (Box 44, Folder 70)
  - Item 1: The Apprentice School, 1948; Publication (Box 44, Folder 70)
- Box: 44, Folder: 71, Publication (Box 44, Folder 71)
  - Item 1: Niagara Mohawk Scholarship Program, Publication (Box 44, Folder 71)
  - Item 2: Age Retirement Allowance Plan, 1963; Publication (Box 44, Folder 71)
  - Item 3: Disability Retirement and Separation Allowance Plan, 1969; Publication (Box 44, Folder 71)
  - Item 4: Disability Retirement and Separation Allowance Plan, 1969; Publication (Box 44, Folder 71)
  - Item 5: Age Retirement Allowance plan, 1969; Publication (Box 44, Folder 71)
- Box: 44, Folder: 72, Publication (Box 44, Folder 72)
  - Item 1: Pushing Pulling and Lifting, 1956; Publication (Box 44, Folder 72)
  - Item 2: Safety Regulations for Stress laboratory, Publication (Box 44, Folder 72)
  - Item 3: Safety Standards covering Pyrophoric Characteristics, 1957; Publication (Box 44, Folder 72)
  - Item 4: Safety Procedure of the Operation of Trichloroethylene Degreasers, 1958; Publication (Box 44, Folder 72)
  - Item 5: Safety Regulations for Using and Handling Rocket Propellants, 1955; Publication (Box 44, Folder 72)
  - Item 6: Safety Regulations, 1955; Publication (Box 44, Folder 72)
  - Item 7: Safety Regulations for Ground Operation of Jet-Propelled Aircraft, 1955; Publication (Box 44, Folder 72)
  - Item 8: Safety and Traffic Rules for the Operation of Vehicles, 1955; Publication (Box 44, Folder 72)
  - Item 9: Safety Standards for High Pressure Gas Systems, 1958; Publication (Box 44, Folder 72)
  - Item 10: Dial File, Publication (Box 44, Folder 72)
  - Item 11: Guide for Professional Drivers, Publication (Box 44, Folder 72)
- Box: 44, Folder: 73, Publication (Box 44, Folder 73)
  - Item 1: An Introduction to Conference Leading, 1952; Publication (Box 44, Folder 73)
- Box: 44, Folder: 74, Publication (Box 44, Folder 74)
  - Item 1: Heaering Conservation, Publication (Box 44, Folder 74)
- Box: 44, Folder: 75, Publication (Box 44, Folder 75)
  - Item 1: Program of Insurance Benefits, 1968; Publication (Box 44, Folder 75)
- Box: 44, Folder: 76, Publication (Box 44, Folder 76)
  - Item 1: Welcome to Northeastern University, Publication (Box 44, Folder 76)
- Box: 44, Folder: 77, Publication (Box 44, Folder 77)
  - Item 1: Profit Sharing at Northland Motors, 1952; Publication (Box 44, Folder 77)
    Author: Julian J. Reiss
- Box: 44, Folder: 78, Publication (Box 44, Folder 78)
  - Item 1: Outline of Bancorporation Pension Plan, 1952; Publication (Box 44, Folder 78)
- Box: 44, Folder: 79, Publication (Box 44, Folder 79)
  - Item 1: Supervision, Publication (Box 44, Folder 79)
- Box: 44, Folder: 80, Publication (Box 44, Folder 80)
  - Item 1: Matching Gifts Plan, Publication (Box 44, Folder 80)
- Box: 44, Folder: 81, Publication (Box 44, Folder 81)
  - Item 1: A Protected Retirement Plan, 1951; Publication (Box 44, Folder 81)
- Box: 44, Folder: 82, Publication (Box 44, Folder 82)
  - Item 1: A Report, 1959; Publication (Box 44, Folder 82)
- Box: 44, Folder: 83, Publication (Box 44, Folder 83)
  - Item 1: Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 44, Folder 83)
- Box: 44, Folder: 84, Publication (Box 44, Folder 84)
  - Item 1: Abstract of Agreement, Publication (Box 44, Folder 84)
- Box: 44, Folder: 85, Publication (Box 44, Folder 85)
  - Item 1: Nunn-Bush Profit Sharing and Retirement Fund, Publication (Box 44, Folder 85)
  - Item 2: The Nunn-Bush 52 Pay Check Plan, 1954; Publication (Box 44, Folder 85)
    Author: William E. McCauley
- Box: 44, Folder: 86, Publication (Box 44, Folder 86)
  - Item 1: Control Systems, Publication (Box 44, Folder 86)
- Box: 44, Folder: 87, Publication (Box 44, Folder 87)
  - Item 1: The Ohio Bell, 1952; Publication (Box 44, Folder 87)
- Box: 44, Folder: 88, Publication (Box 44, Folder 88)
  - Item 1: A Record of Achievement, 1958; Publication (Box 44, Folder 88)
- Box: 44, Folder: 89, Publication (Box 44, Folder 89)
  - Item 1: Keep 'em Rolling Safely, Publication (Box 44, Folder 89)
  - Item 2: How to Stay in One Place Around Your Service Station, 1955; Publication (Box 44, Folder 89)
  - Item 3: Safety Color Code, Publication (Box 44, Folder 89)
  - Item 4: Safety Manual for Bulk Plant Operation, 1953; Publication (Box 44, Folder 89)
- Box: 44, Folder: 90, Publication (Box 44, Folder 90)
  - Item 1: Life Insurance and Death Benefit Plan, 1957; Publication (Box 44, Folder 90)
  - Item 2: Hospitalization Plan for Retired Employees, 1955; Publication (Box 44, Folder 90)
  - Item 3: Hospitalization Plan, 1953; Publication (Box 44, Folder 90)
  - Item 4: Scholarship Plan, 1953; Publication (Box 44, Folder 90)
  - Item 5: A Savings Program For Employees, 1956; Publication (Box 44, Folder 90)
  - Item 6: Accident and Sick Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 44, Folder 90)
  - Item 7: Accidental Death and Dismemberment Insurance Plan, 1957; Publication (Box 44, Folder 90)
  - Item 8: Retirement Plan, 1957; Publication (Box 44, Folder 90)
  - Item 9: Policy Guide for Employees, 1955; Publication (Box 44, Folder 90)
  - Item 10: Scott Salaried Employees Vacation Plan, Publication (Box 44, Folder 90)
  - Item 11: The Ohio Oil Company Marketing Training Program, Publication (Box 44, Folder 90)